<!--- This file is part of the RKWard project (https://rkward.kde.org).
SPDX-FileCopyrightText: by Thomas Friedrichsmeier <thomas.friedrichsmeier@kdemail.net>
SPDX-FileContributor: The RKWard Team <rkward-devel@kde.org>
SPDX-License-Identifier: GPL-2.0-or-later
-->
<document>
	<snippet id="dialog_settings">
		<caption title="Generic settings"/>
		<setting id="mode">Specify the quantity to be calculated (probabilities, densities, or quantiles), and the quantity given (probabilities or quantiles)</setting>
		<setting id="n_quantiles">When calculating densities or probabilities, specify the number of evenly spaces quantiles to show. Alternatively, use the setting above.</setting>
		<setting id="q">When calculating densities or probabilities, specify one or more quantiles. Alternatively, leave this empty to use the setting above, instead.</setting>
		<setting id="n_probabilities">When calculating quantiles, specify the number of evenly spaced probabilities (optionally logarithmic) to show. Alternatively, use the setting below.</setting>
		<setting id="p">When calculating quantiles, specify one or more probabilities, optionally logarithmic (see below). If this setting is left empty, the setting above is used, instead.</setting>
		<setting id="logp">When calculating probabilities, return these as log (p). When specifying probabilities, these are supplied as log (p).</setting>
		<setting id="logd">When calculating densities, return these as log (d).</setting>
		<setting id="lower">If checked (the default) probabilities are P[X ≤ x]. Otherwise (upper tail) probabilities are P[X &gt; x]</setting>
		<setting id="preview">Show a preview of the result.</setting>
		<caption title="Distribution specific settings"/>
	</snippet>
	<snippet id="dialog_usage">
		<usage>Select the desired mode of operation, then specify the values of interest. The input values (quantiles or probabilities) can be left empty, in which case a short sequence of evenly spaced values will be filled in, automatically.</usage>
	</snippet>
</document>
